A Guide to the Shelton-Winn-Oliver Family Papers, 1764-1965
Library of Virginia
- Subject Files. (Box 9-32)
  - Estate of John M. Greenlee (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Estate of John Harlow (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Estate of Meriwether Jones (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Estate of Henry King - Accounts and Receipts, 1820-1829 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Estate of Henry King - Accounts and Receipts, 1830-1839 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Estate of Henry King - Accounts and Receipts, 1840-1849 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Estate of Henry King - Accounts and Receipts, 1850-1855 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Estate of Henry King - Bonds and Promissory Notes (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Estate of Henry King - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Estate of Henry King - Fee Bills (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Estate of Henry King - Inventory and Appraisement (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Estate of Henry King - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Estate of Henry King - Richmond Property (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Estate of Henry King - Sale of Lots (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Estate of Henry King - Suit Papers (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Estate of Henry King - Tax Receipts (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Estate of Henry King - Vouchers for Private Account with Abner Robinson (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Estate of Robert King (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Estate of Thomas King (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Estate of Henry Lefevre (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Estate of William Lumpkin (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Estate of John Mann (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Estate of Austin Morris (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Estate of John T. O'Harrow (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Estate of Isaac Oliver (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Estate of John Pate (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Estate of Maria W. Pate (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Estate of Sarah Patmon (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Estate of Michel Picot de Boisfeillet (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Estate of Stephen Pulliam (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Estate of Fendall Ragland (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Estate of Jesse Rice (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Estate of John Richardson - Accounts and Receipts (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Estate of John Richardson - Fee Bills (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Estate of Joanna Robinson (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Estate of Silas Shelburn (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Estate of Maud G. Shelton (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Estate of Mosby Sheppard (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Estate of John Snead (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Estate of Joseph Starke (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Estate of John Street, Jr. (Box 18, Folder 7a)
  - Estate of Col. Parke Street - Accounts and Receipts (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
  - Estate of Col. Parke Street - Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Estate of Col. Parke Street - Fee Bills (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Estate of Col. Parke Street - Inventory and Appraisement (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Estate of Col. Parke Street - Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Estate of Col. Parke Street - Sales (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Estate of Col. Parke Street - Suit Papers (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Estate of Col. Parke Street - Tax Receipts (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Estate of Jacob K. Strong (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Estate of Nelson Thacker (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Estate of Garland Thompson (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Estate of Charles Tinsley (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
  - Estate of Ann S. Vest (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Estate of Isaac Wingfield (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Estate of Jesse Winn - Accounts and Receipts (Vouchers) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Estate of Jesse Winn - Sales (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Estate of William R. Winn (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Estate of Peter Winston - Accounts and Receipts (Box 19, Folder 6-10)
  - Estate of Peter Winston - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Estate of Peter Winston - Fee Bills (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Estate of Peter Winston - Inventory and Appraisement (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Estate of Peter Winston - Suit Papers (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Estate of Peter Winston - Tax Receipts (Box 19, Folder 14a)
  - Estate of Peter Winston - Wingfield Administration (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Estate of Philip H. Winston (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Estate of Polly Woodfin (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Faudree (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Fee Bills, 1811-1818 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fee Bills, 1820-1829 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Fee Bills, 1830-1839 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fee Bills, 1840-1849 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fee Bills, 1850-1859 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fee Bills, 1860-1873 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fees Due - Superior Court of Law and County Court, 1822 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fifas (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fleming vs. Mallory et al. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Flemming, John A. - Civil War Letters (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fontaine vs. Wingfield's admrs. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Forage Requisition, 1862 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Ford's Hotel (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fortune, James (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fostaine et al vs. Wingfield admr. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Fox vs. Page's guardian (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Francis, John B. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - From Spotsylvania Onward, 1898 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Genealogical Notes (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Gilman (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Ginter, Lewis - Accounts, 1850-1851 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Glazebrook (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Glinn v. Fleming (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Goddin & Apperson (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Gold Values (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Goodman vs. Smith (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - John N. Gordon's Sons (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Green (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Green exr. vs. Smith (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Green vs. Tinsley exor. (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Green, Fleming (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Greenlee, Mary Jane - Writing Exercises Book (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Grubbs, James T. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Grubbs & Apperson (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Grubbs & Williams (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Guardian Accounts - J. Alexander Brown, 1854 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Guardian Accounts - J. Alexander Brown, 1855-April 1856 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Guardian Accounts - J. Alexander Brown, April 1856-April 1857 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Guardian Accounts - J. Alexander Brown, 1857-1858 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Guardian Accounts - J. Alexander Brown, 1858-1859 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Guardian Accounts - J. Alexander Brown, 1859-1860 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Guardian Accounts - J. Alexander Brown, 1860-1861 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Guardian Accounts - Martha R. Brown, 1854 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Guardian Accounts - Martha R. Brown, 1855-April 1856 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Guardian Accounts - Martha R. Brown, April 1856-April 1857 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Guardian Accounts - Martha R. Brown, 1857-1858 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Guardian Accounts - Martha R. Brown, 1858-1859 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Guardian Accounts - Martha R. Brown, 1859-1860 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Guardian Accounts - Martha R. Brown, 1860-1862 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary J. Brown, 1854 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary J. Brown, April 1855-April 1856 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary J. Brown, April 1856-April 1957 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary J. Brown, 1857-1858 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary J. Brown, 1858-1859 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary J. Brown, 1859-1860 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary J. Brown, 1860-1861 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Guardian Accounts - Sarah Eliza Brown, 1854 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Guardian Accounts - Sarah Eliza Brown, 1855-April 1856 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Guardian Accounts - Sarah Eliza Brown, April 1856-April 1857 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Guardian Accounts - Sarah Eliza Brown, 1857-1858 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Guardian Accounts - Sarah Eliza Brown, 1858-1859 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Guardian Accounts - Sarah Eliza Brown, 1859-1860 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Guardian Accounts - Sarah Eliza Brown, 1860-1861 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Guardian Accounts - Brown's Heirs, 1852-April 1857 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Guardian Accounts - Brown's Heirs, 1857-1858 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Guardian Accounts - Brown's Heirs, 1858-1859 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Guardian Accounts - Brown's Heirs, 1859-1860 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Guardian Accounts - Brown's Heirs, 1860-1861 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary Flemming (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Guardian Accounts - John M. Francis (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Guardian Accounts - Glinn (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Guardian Accounts - Elizabeth M. Sheppard (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Guardian Accounts - John M. Sheppard (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Guardian Accounts - Maria L. Sheppard (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Guardian Accounts - Martha E. Sheppard (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Guardian Accounts - Mary G.C. Sheppard (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Guardian Accounts - Susan A. Sheppard (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Hackett (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Hall vs. Hall (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Hands Accounts (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Hanover County Farm Bureau (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hanover County Soil Conservation Association, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Hanover Garden Club (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hanover Woman's Club (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - James G. Hardy; Smith vs. Hardy (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Harris (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Harris et als vs. Bumpass et als. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Haw, George E. - Hanover County History (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Haxall & Crenshaw (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Hendrick (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Henley, Robert Y. - Subscription List, 1849 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Hines (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Hogg vs. Eubank (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Hollins Institute (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Hooper, Edward W. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - House Accountd (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Hudgins (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Hudson et als vs. Montgomery et als. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Hull vs. Murray et als. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Hundley (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - George A. Hundley & Co. (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - A.A. Hutcheson (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Hutzler, Charles (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Inaugural Addresses, 1918, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Public Affairs (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Invitations and Announcements (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Jackson & Dunlop (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - James (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Jesse admr vs. DeJarnette (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Johnson (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Jones, D.L. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Jones vs. King (Jones, David R.) (Box 23, Folder 2a)
  - Jones et als vs. Jones et als. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Jones, C.B. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Gustavus V. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Isabella (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Thomas L. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - W.M. Jones & Co. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Keesee & Parr (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - J.B. Kidd (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Kilby (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - King & Todd (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - R.T. Knox & Bro. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Korb et als vs. Underwood et als. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Lacy vs. Cross et als. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Ladd, William P. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - John M. Lamb (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Lambert vs. Lambert (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Land, Helen (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Land Papers (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Lankford (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Law License (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Lawrence/Eddleton (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Lawson, Mary W. (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Lawson, Mary W. - Accounts and Vouchers, 1841-1845 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Lawson, Mary W. - Accounts and Vouchers, 1846-1848 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Leadbetter, Peter H. (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - William Leach; R.R. Howison (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Lee, Alfred (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Levy Brothers (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Ligon vs. Woodson (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Linen Inventory (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - List of Insolvents and Non-Residents, 1795 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Lists of Fees Due/Received (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Little (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Lumpkin, William w/ Baker, Samuel (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Lyle vs. Curtis admr. (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Mallory (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Mallory, Lewis (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Mallory vs. DeJarnette admr. (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Manning (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Marriage License - Doswell/Davenport, 1868 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Marshall, J.F. (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Martin, Brown & Cardozo (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Martin vs. Tinsbloom (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Matthews (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mayo & James (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - McCauley vs. Hardaway (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - J.V.L. McCreery (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - McDowell, Andrew (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - McDowell County Bible Society (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - McGregor, Robert F. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - McRae (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Mead vs. Tredegar Iron Co. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Melton (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Military Discharge, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Military Resignations (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Militia Commission, 1861 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Heath J. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Mills et als vs. Winston exrs. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Mills' Lawsuits (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Minister's Return - Carter/Snead, 1833 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Minutes, Winn's Meeting House, 3 July 1830 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 19-21)
  - Miscellaneous Suit Papers (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Mississippi Land (D. Comfort) (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Montgomery, Charles R. (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Moore (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Moran (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Morris vs. Lumpkin (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Mosby, John - Insurance Policy, 1837 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Mosby vs. Wickham (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Muncas (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Muster Fines (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Nash (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Nelson et als. vs. Burwell et als. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Subscription & Advertisement Receipts (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Newton, Willoughby - "Westwood" Sale (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Nicholas vs. Foster admr. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Nixon, George R. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - G.A. Nolting (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Notary Public (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Notice of Lands for Rent, 1864 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Nuckols (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - G. Ober & Sons (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Orders for Payment or Goods (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Orders to Pay Witnesses (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Overseers of the Poor - Hanover County (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Painting (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Palmer (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Parrish vs. Spindle admr. (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Parrish vs. Winston et als. (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Parrish & Tinsley vs. Massie (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Pate (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Patent, 1828 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Patmon (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Patrick Henry Memorial Highway (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Pendleton, Joseph W. - Ditching by Slave Billy (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Perkins (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Perrin (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Photographs (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Poetry, Sermons, etc. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Poll for Magistrate, Hanover County, 1864 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Pollard (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Pollard, Dr. Thomas (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Pool, E.B. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Postcards (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Postcard Album (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Powers of Attorney (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - L. Powers & Son (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Prescription (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Price (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Price et al vs. Barker (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Priddy (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Production Credit Association - Rules, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Proprietors of Richmond Whig vs. Tomlin (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Protection Paper, 1864 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Pryor (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Publications (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Pulliam vs. Starke admr. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Purcell & Ladd (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Puryear (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Quarles, Thomas D. (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Ratcliffe (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Ratcliffe, James W. (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Recipes (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Redd vs. Brock (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Reed & Bayley (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Regimental Orders, 1859, 1861 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Report Cards (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Richardson admr vs. Anderson admr. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Richardson vs. Richardson (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Richardson admr vs Richardson et als. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Road Map of Hanover County, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Road Papers (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - J. & M. Rosenbaum (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Rural Plains Nursery (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Sacra (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Salem Church - Membership List, 1912 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Saunders (Box 27, Folder 10-13)
  - Schaffer (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - School Exercises (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Seddon admr vs. Morris (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Sheilds & Cary (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Shelton (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Shelton & Dyer vs. Miller (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Shelton Family Bible Records (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Sheppard, John M. (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Sheppard, Mary G.C. (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Short (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Simpson, Bass & Co. (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Sittser (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Skipwith vs. Isbell (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Slacum, Benjamin (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Slave Bills of Sale (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Slave Pass, 1835 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Slave Runaway, 1855 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Smith (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Smith, Thomas A. (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - William Ira Smith & Co. (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Snead (Box 27, Folder 34-35)
  - Snead vs. Davis (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Snead vs. RF & P Railroad Co. (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Southern Fertilizing Company (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Speech of Gov. Josiah Martin, Newbern, NC, 4 April 1775 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - E.B. Spence (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Spencer vs. Greenlee admr (Slave Values), 1828 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Stanley vs. Patteson (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - P.H. Starke (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Stebbins (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Stock Certificate - Richmond and Charlottesville Turnpike Company, 1855 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Stockdell, Judith A.E. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - A.Y. Stokes & Co. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Stone (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Street, Charles P. - Bonds (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Street, Joseph H. - Bonds (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Street, Mary R. - Bonds (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Street, Samuel G. - Bonds (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Stubbs (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Subscription to Buy Horse for Rev. Paxton, 1862 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Sublett & Bro. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Sublett & Co. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Summonses (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Surveys (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Talbott & Sons (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Taliaferro, John H. (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Taliaferro vs. Anderson (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Talley (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Tax Receipts, 1813-1819 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Tax Receipts, 1820-1829 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Tax Receipts, 1830-1839 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Tax Receipts, 1840-1849 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Tax Receipts, 1850-1859 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Tax Receipts, 1860-1869 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Tax Receipts, 1870-1874 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Tax Receipts, 1883, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Taylor (Box 28, Folder 34-36)
  - Taylor, C.H. (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - E.B. Taylor (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Taylor, Tazewell, 1872-1873 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Taylor vs. Robinson's admr. (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Terrell (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - Thacker (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Thacker vs. Thacker et als. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Thomas, Benjamin (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Thomas vs. Brown (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Thompson (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Thompson vs. Thompson admr. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Timberlake, George (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Tinsley (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Toler (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tomkies (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Truehart vs. Mann (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Tucker Family Genealogical Notes (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Tukey (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Vaughan, Edwin (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Vaughan, James W. (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Vest (Box 29, Folder 18-20)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Virginia: The Rose of the South (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Tech Student Handbook, 1939-1940 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Vores (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Wade (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Walker (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - War Ration Books (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Ware, A.G. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Wash vs. Woodson et al. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - George Watt & Co. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - West & Johnston (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Wheat (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - White (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
  - White, Chastain (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - White, Warner - Bonds (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Wicker vs. Terry et als. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Wickham (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Will of Robert Anderson (Box 30, Folder 12a)
  - Will of Nathaniel Bacon, 1692 (copy) (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Will of Edward S. Barker (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Will of James Brown (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Will of Walter Coles (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Will of John Darracott (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Will of Thomas Doswell (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Will of Peter Foster (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Will of John B. Green (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Will of Mary Jennings (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Will of Lewis Kimbrough (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Will of Henry King (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Will of John F. Lucord (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Will of Austin Morris (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Will of Isaac Oliver (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Will of Moses Parsons (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Will of Col. Parke Street (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Will of Louisa Thacker (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Will of Wyatt Tinsley (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Will of Peter Winston (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Will of Richard M. Winston (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Willson vs. Willson (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Wiltshire (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Wingfield, Ira (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Wingfield vs. Morris (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Wingfield vs. Wingfield admrs. (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Winston (Box 30, Folder 38-39)
  - Winston, B.L. (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Winston admx vs. England admr. (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Winston exrs vs. Timberlake (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Winston exrs vs. Wingfield et als. (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Winston et als vs. Winston et als. (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Winston vs. Powers (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Woltz (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Wood (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Woodson (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Woodson vs. Goodman (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Woodson vs. Hargrove (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Wrappers (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Wynne, A.E. (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Yarbrough (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Postal Covers and Envelopes (Box 31)
  - Stamps and Postmarks (Box 32)
- Ledgers (Box 33-36)
  - Account and Mmemorandum Book of James Hervey Greenlee, 1829-1851 (Box 33)
  - Account Book for James and Benjamin Oliver's Hanover County Store, 1790-1791 (Box 33)
  - Daybook for John and Benjamin Oliver's Caroline County Store, 13 May 1799-3 June 1800 (Box 33)
  - Daybook for James and Benjamin Oliver's Hanover County Store, 21 October 1790-10 November 1791, 1 November 1794-12 February 1796 (Box 34)
  - Daybook for James and Benjamin Oliver's Caroline County Store, 15 November 1794-29 June 1797 (Box 34)
  - Account Book, 1775-1784 (portion) (Box 35)
  - Account and Memorandum Book, 1821-1842 (Box 35)
  - J.H. Greenlee's Tan Yard Book, 1842-1874 (Box 35)
  - Ledger A for James and Benjamin Oliver's Caroline County Store, 1794-1812 (original and bound photostatic copy) (Box 36)
- Oversize (Box 37)
  - Accounts and Receipts (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Advertisement for Carter Glass Biography, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Affidavit, 1819 (Box 37, Folder 2a)
  - Changes by Local Board of Equalization of Values Assessed (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Chattahoochee County, Georgia ROTC Manual Map (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Commissions, 1916-1917 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Confederate Bond (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Deeds (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Genealogical Charts (blank) (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Hollins Institute Illustration (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Hollywood Cemetery Map (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Insurance Policy, 1818 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - "The Life annd Public Services of William Henry Harrison" (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - "The Lost Cause" - Currier & Ives, 1871 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Plats and Surveys (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Richmond Weekly Examiner, 8 August 1848 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Roosevelt/Garner Election Posters (Box 37, Folder 16)